[{"answer": "Well, I can't really predict but I think you're right.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 48, "question": "What do you think will happen?", "qSentId": 47}, {"answer": "Yes, and don't you love, by the way, Cardinal O'Malley out of Boston, Cardinal Dolan out of New York.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Am I right?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "I would say there are really two areas.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "So what is your sense about the kind of reform, which a new Pope may look to successfully push through?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "I did speak to him yesterday.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "Does he believe he has a chance?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "But, also, I think the key word is energy.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "And how are you going to be more attractive and joyful than Cardinal Timothy Dolan?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "UINN: Nothing.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "What is wrong with that?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "I do because my fear is, my belief is that with food-related issues, which are different, which are more complicated because unlike smoking which you can stop and continue existing, you have to interact with food at least three times a day.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Do you believe he's wrong about this?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Are you giving me 100 percent guarantee you will not meddle in things that people eat or drink?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "You know, you have to be for your hometown guy.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Do you have a view on the Pope, by the way?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "Well, I am for Christine Quinn, but it's a wide open race.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Who would be the next mayor of New York?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "UINN: It was great.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "How did you feel about that?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Well, we -- when we launched the campaign -- actually we kicked it off with a walk and talk tour.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Have you thought about what yours might be?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "A walk and talk.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "Say that again?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "You know, I think you want to help folks move up, right, and the only way I got this job, my first job in New York City as tenant housing organizer, I called people.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Do you believe in doing that, or is it purely on merit?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Push ahead.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 315, "question": "What is the secret to getting to where you've got to?", "qSentId": 314}, {"answer": "Well, hello, Piers.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "Is she right that too many women lean back rather than lean in when it comes to promoting themselves and being ambitious?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "Yes, and yes.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "Are women basically a bit nicer than men in the workplace and does that consequentially hold them back?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Marissa Mayer is in a very unique situation.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Or is Marissa Mayer going to be in the minority when most women want to have flexi time and maybe work a bit from home?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "Even when that's not possible -- I remember my chief of staff was pregnant with her baby, and I encouraged her, look, we work ridiculous hours in Congress, bring your daughter to work, we'll use the pack 'n play.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Wouldn't that help?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "(on camera): This is a Bushmaster?", "qSentId": 580}, {"answer": "Well, like you, I knew what the law was.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "Were you surprised, Hillary, at the ease with which you bought that rifle?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "I am an American citizen and resident.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Are you an American citizen or resident?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Well, legally, you're supposed to be an American citizen.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "You could have been a British citizen and still done the same thing?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "No, of course not.", "docId": "130311pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "What did you do with it?", "qSentId": 625}]